Carlos Alberto Monastyrski

♦ Huelva, Huelva, Spain 🗷 charly.monastyrski@gmail.com 🛘 +34604954584 🛅 /carlos-monastyrski

SUMMARY

Experienced software engineer with a comprehensive 5-year bachelor's degree in engineering and ongoing pursuit of a master's degree. Backed by over one and a half year of professional experience, I am driven to propel my career forward by embracing continuous learning and tackling intricate projects. Committed to amplifying my skill repertoire, I am poised to contribute enthusiastically to innovative and demanding endeavors.

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Ensolvers

- · Tasks:
- Team leader of a group of five developers
- Full-stack web development, maintaining existing functionalities and creating new complete functionalities
- Customer support with direct communication with the customer
- Coaching of new members and interview new candidates
- · Technologies:
- Java 11/17, Spring Boot, Hibernate, JPA
- PostgreSQL/MySql
- AWS Cloud Services (S3, ECS, CloudWatch, SES, SNS, etc.)
- React

QA Tester

Vates

July 2021 - February 2022, Córdoba, Argentina

February 2022 - Present, San Francisco, USA

- · Created and executed automated software test plans, cases and scripts to uncover, identify and document software problems and their causes
- · Learned automated testing with Selenium

Researcher development

Universidad Tecnológica Nacional

March 2020 - December 2021, Córdoba, Argentina

- · Analysis and detection of patterns in a conceptual graph constructed from textual written answers to questions on a specific topic.
- Built RESTful APIs with FastAPI, receiving data from a GraphQL database
- Creation of new functionalities for an ASP.NET application
- Collaboration with 5 university tutors and 3 other students in an agile methodology.
- · Technologies:
- Python FastAPI
- ASP.NET
- GraphQL

EDUCATION

Master's degree in computer engineering

Universidad de Huelva · Huelva, Spain · 2023 · 9.01

Information Systems Engineering

Information Systems Engineering · Córdoba, Argentina · 2021 · 9,12

SKILLS

 $React\ , Java,\ Spring\ Boot,\ Hibernate,\ SQL\ and\ NoSQL\ databases,\ Python,\ Django,\ Node. js,\ NestJs,\ Hadoop,\ Spark,\ Kafka,\ Redis,\ AWS,\ GCP$